

A passionate programmer and web developer having **2 years** of experience in designing and developing efficient web and mobile apps. An enthusiastic learner who is committed to building efficient, maintainable, scalable and reusable solutions using strong analytical skills.

## CONTACT

PHONE: +91 7619389333

Linked In https://www.linkedin.com/in/manjun ath-hegade-082067170/

GitHub https://github.com/Manjunathhegade

EMAIL: manjunathhegadesmg@gmail.com

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- Innovation
- Effective communication
- Flexible and adaptable
- Leadership
- Problem solving
- Time management

# **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Kannada
- Hindi (Conversational)
- Telugu (Basic)

# Manjunath Hegade DR

Full stack Developer

# **EDUCATION**

# Shree devi institute of technology, Mangalore (CSE)

2015 - 2019 CGPA: 7.0

University- Visvesvaraya technical university (VTU), Belgaum.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Happiest Minds Technologies Ltd - L&D

18/09/2019 - 25/10/2019

- Worked as training coordinator under learning and development team
- Maintaining and evaluating training performance of the candidate.
- Organizing conferences and lecturing sessions.

## Mediclog Services Pvt Ltd - Software engineer

Nov-2019 - Present

Medicloq is a startup and product based company. Developing and maintaining Ambulance booking projects.

- Designing and developing user interfaces using React and React Material UI working closely with UX designers.
- Designing Database, creating and maintaining tables in MongoDB.
- Writing API methods in Express JS to interact with MongoDB.
- Creating reusable components.
- Maintaining and deploying react projects.
- Creating and developing System design & architecture.
- Integrating SMS gateway to Express JS (backend) application.
- Coordinating and maintaining projects and Team.
- Used JIRA as the bug tracking system to track and maintain the history of bugs/tasks/issues on every day bases.
- Set up GitLab as building and maintaining Teams repository and braches.

## **SKILLS**

